## **NADZEYA DUNAYEVA**

# **Software Tester**

### Remote

+46707783754 nadiadunaeva@gmail.com github.com/nadiadunaeva

#### **SUMMARY**

As a dedicated Software Tester with 1.5 years of experience and a strong background in marketing and e-commerce, I am eager to contribute my skills to innovative projects and advance in the software engineering field. I bring a deep understanding of various testing tools and methodologies, strong analytical skills, attention to detail, and the ability to work well both independently and as part of a team. By combining my marketing expertise with software testing experience, I am confident I would make a valuable addition to a company looking for a software tester.

Work authorization: Temporary residence for 2 years in Sweden.

## **SKILLS**

Software Testing, Postman, Git, Chrome DevTools, Jira, Charles Proxy, JavaScript, HTML/ CSS, Agile/Scrum, React.js, Web APIs, Webstorm, VS Code, E-commerce marketing, Google Analytics.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Software Tester

InsightWhale, Remote | March 2021 - August 2021

- Conducted testing of marketing analytics tools implementation according to project documentation.
- Reported and tracked issues using Jira, and worked closely with analytics team to resolve issues.
- Tested the implementation of A/B testing variations and events according to documentation.
- Worked closely with cross-functional teams, including marketing and product development, to ensure seamless integration of QA processes.

Tools: Google Analytics, Amplitude, Google Tag Manager, Google DevTools, Jira.

## Marketplace Specialist

Arteza, Minsk, Belarus | November 2018 - February 2020

- Developed marketing paid campaign strategy for a US-based company on the Amazon EU marketplace.
- Conducted QA testing to ensure the accurate setup and execution of marketing paid campaigns on the Amazon EU marketplace.
- Tracked and analyzed marketplaces' key performance indicators (KPIs) to drive brand sales.
- Utilized various marketing tools to monitor campaign performance, identify areas for improvement, and created marketing documentation via Jira and Confluence.

*Tools*: Amazon Marketplace, Jungle Scout, Helium10, Key Collector, Google Analytics, Excel, Jira, Slack.

## Software Tester

Modus, Minsk, Belarus | June 2017 - June 2018

- Conducted a variety of testing activities, including post-release, web, and mobile API testing.
- Ensured QA of publicly available mobile (android, ios) and web applications for car fleet monitoring.
- Utilized Agile/Scrum methodology for testing processes, worked closely with the development team.
- Created project test documentation and reported issues tracking with Jira.
- Maintained effective communication within Jira and Slack to track project tasks, resolve issues, and collaborate with team members.

Tools: Charles Proxy, Postman, Hockeyapp, Google Developer tools, Testrail, BrowserStack, Jira, Onesky.

## **Marketing Specialist**

Qmedia, Minsk, Belarus | September 2015 - June 2017

- Managed and optimized online advertising campaigns in Google Ads for diverse clients.
- Conducted comprehensive campaign analysis using marketing analytics tools to optimize performance.
- Devised effective advertising strategies and successfully implemented them through advertising campaigns.
- Created project test documentation and reported issues tracking with Jira.

Tools: Google Adwords, Google Analytics, Excel, Google Tag Manager.

#### **EDUCATION**

September 2010 - June 2015 Belarusian State University, Minsk, Belarus

#### **COURSES**

IT-INCUBATOR, Remote | Software Development | December 2022 - May 2023

- Frontend pet projects: <u>Todo list\_developed using React and TypeScript.</u>
- <u>Personal blog</u> website, <u>dice game</u> project developed with <u>JavaScript</u>, <u>HTML</u>, and <u>CSS</u>.

Technologies: React, TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, GitHub, VS Code, Chrome Devtools, Webstorm.

Swedish Language | March 2020 - August 2021 - SFI and SVA beginner-level courses

### **CERTIFICATES**

Web application development with JS Certificate

Google Tag Manager

AWS Cloud Quest: Cloud Practitioner

## **LANGUAGES**

English (professional)

Swedish (intermediate)

Russian (native)